

BRIAN HERNANDEZ

— UI/Graphic Designer —

CONTACT DETAILS



Prgy. San Antonio, San Pedro, Laguna

**** 0917 773 33 00

bbhernandez@gmail.com

www.artstation.com/br1an23

f /br1an23

EDUCATION -



2002

B.S. INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Colegio de San Juan de Letran - Calamba

SKILLS -



Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe XD

Adobe Premiere

Adobe After Effects

Microsoft Word

Microsoft Powerpoint

EXPERIENCE SUMMARY



Graphic Designer

Sales/Marketing Manager

User Interface Designer

Game Artist

Web Designer

Product Design

REFERENCE -



RAYMOND FABELLA

UI/UX Designer

Innspire Intelligent Hotels Philippines

Phone: 09228338490

Email: mon.fabella@gmail.com

PROFILE -



Creative and hard working graphic designer with keen eye for details. I have a unique mix of creativity, time management, problem solving, and technical skills proven by more than Twenty (20) years of experience. Skilled with Adobe Creative Suite and Microsof Office. Excellent management of the complete design process, from conceptualization to delivery. Expert at interdepartmental coordination and communication.

WORK EXPERIENCE —



November 2023 - Present

UI DESIGNER | 3J Pearl Plaza 88

User Interface Design; Web design (browser and mobile); Create animated web banners; Web mockups, prototypes, and designs; Coordinate with web dev team.

November 2021 - April 2023

UI DESIGNER | Fun6 Tech

User Interface Design; Web design (browser and mobile); Create animated web banners; Web mockups, prototypes, and designs; Coordinate with web dev team.

November 2021 - November 2023

CREATIVE DIRECTOR | Skin Solutions Cosmeceuticals Inc.

Create design for skin care products including logo, packaging and design guidelines.

February 2019 - October 2021

SALES & MARKETING MANAGER | JeorgiaMed Inc.

Generating unique sales plans. Creating engaging advertisements, emails, and promotional literature. Developing pricing strategies. Create meeting & marketing materials. Sales human resource objectives. Develop and create company profile, including logo, brochures, and website.

October 2017 - January 2019

UI DESIGNER | Vertex Digital Entertainment Technologies Inc.

User Interface Design; Web design (browser and mobile); Create web banners and other promotions; Create web templates and assets; Web mockups, prototypes, and designs; Coordinate with web dev team.

February 2017 - October 2017

UI DESIGNER I Arriba Universal Inc.

User Interface design; Web design, mockups and prototypes; Create animated web banners and other promotional assets; Create web templates.

September 2002 - October 2016

UI MANAGER | Internet Empire Technology Co. Ltd (Taiwan)

UI DESIGNER | Global Nations, Inc. (Philippines)

UI & GRAPHIC DESIGNER | Denizen Technologies, Inc. (Philippines)

LEAD GAME ARTIST | Gonzogames Philippines Inc.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | Ahjee! Philippines

I.T. ADMINISTRATOR | Hakats Sdn. Bhd. (Brunei Darussalam)

TRANINGS & SEMINARS —



May 22 - 24, 2012 | CASUAL CONNECT ASIA 2012 | Participant

Suntec Convention Center, Singapore

April 25, 2008 | BROADBAND AWARENESS PROGRAM | Participant

Telekom Brunei Headquarters, Bandar Seri Begawan, Brunei Darussalam

September 7 - 8, 2005 | NATIONAL SUMMIT ON INFORMATION SOCIETY | Delegate International Convention Centre, Bandar Seri Begawan, Brunei Darussalam

August 2005 | INITIATIVE FOR ASEAN INTEGRATION : CAPACITY BUILDING PROGRAM FOR PUBLIC SECTOR OF CAMBODIA, LAOS, MYANMAR AND VIETNAM | Assistant Trainer

Phnom Pehn, Kingdom of Cambodia

July 2005 | Council for Administrative Reform

PR-003: Web Administration and Web Authoring | Assistant Trainer

Phnom Pehn, Kingdom of Cambodia